Unlock the power within.
The Tiger's Apprentice is a animation, family, fantasy
film directed by Raman Hui Shing-Ngai.
After the death of his grandmother, Tom Lee discovers he is part of a
long lineage of magical protectors known as the Guardians.
With guidance from a mythical tiger named Hu and the other Zodiac animal
warriors, Tom trains to take on an evil force that threatens humanity.
Tom Lee (voice), played by Brandon Soo Hoo.
Hu (voice), played by Henry Golding.
Nua Kua / Cynthia (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Mistral (voice), played by Sandra Oh.
Loo (voice), played by Michelle Yeoh.
Sidney (voice), played by Bowen Yang.
The Tiger's Apprentice is a 2024 American animated fantasy
film based on the 2003 novel by Laurence Yep.
Produced by Paramount Animation and Jane Startz Productions, it is directed by Raman Hui and co-directed by Paul Watling
and Yong Duk Jhun (in their directorial debuts) from a screenplay by David Magee and Christopher Yost.
The film stars the voices of Brandon Soo Hoo, Henry
Golding, Lucy Liu, Sandra Oh, and Michelle Yeoh.
Cartoon Network originally opted to produce a live-action/CG hybrid television film
adaptation of the novel in the late 2000s, but it never came to fruition.
Paramount later acquired the rights for an animated film in
March 2019, with Carlos Baena attached as director.
Mikros Animation provided animation.
Much of the voice cast was revealed between 2020 and 2022,
following Golding's casting in July 2020.
Hui later replaced Baena as director in January 2022.
Steve Jablonsky composed the score.
Originally planned for theatrical release by Paramount Pictures, The Tiger's Apprentice was released on
Paramount+ on February 2, 2024, after being delayed several times due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of tiger, apprentice, based on
children's book, chinese zodiac signs, apprenticeship.